<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tweak on Effective Eureka</title>
    <link>http://ee.cor.ninja/tags/tweak/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tweak on Effective Eureka</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ee.cor.ninja/tags/tweak/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Birth</title>
      <link>http://ee.cor.ninja/post/birth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ee.cor.ninja/post/birth/</guid>
      <description>The biological processes of reproduction and birth combine elements of Origin and Tweak.
Tweak is used to arrange the biological elements, but the person does not become complete without Origin placing the soul or center of the being and attaching it to the rest of the matter.
Importantly, this does not mean that something has to die, or lose its soul in the other realm, but rather some amount of disorganized matter is organized upon transition from the other realm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools</title>
      <link>http://ee.cor.ninja/post/schools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ee.cor.ninja/post/schools/</guid>
      <description>In this as yet unnamed universe, there 3 of schools magic. They are as follows:
 Origination - or &amp;ldquo;Origin&amp;rdquo; for short, creative magic Suppression - or &amp;ldquo;Quell&amp;rdquo; for short, destructive magic Transformation - or &amp;ldquo;Tweak&amp;rdquo; for short, manipulative magic  Each kind of magic follows some rules of conservation of energy, mass, or magic, but depend on the introduction of two realms or states of being so that any kind of energy, mass or other material property can exist in either realm and has a sort of parallel void in the inverse realm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>